<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en_us"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en_us" /><updated>2024-12-23T00:00:19+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Think Flow</title><entry><title type="html">How to start journaling for life change in 2025</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/How-to-start-journaling-for-life-change-in-2025/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to start journaling for life change in 2025" /><published>2024-12-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/How%20to%20start%20journaling%20for%20life%20change%20in%202025</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/How-to-start-journaling-for-life-change-in-2025/"><![CDATA[<p>I have always been a massive fan of writing for personal use. For that reason, I have been journaling since I was 16.<br />
Initially, I didn’t know what to write about, but eventually, when I kept writing, it changed my life. <br />
So, I am presenting you with a 30-day challenge to try journalling and see how it changes your life.<br />
If you’re wondering how keeping a journal might benefit you, here are some that may help you:</p>
<h3 id="benefits-of-journalling">Benefits of Journalling.</h3>
<ol>
  <li><strong>Makes you boost your mood.</strong><br />
 If you’re feeling down or having a rough day, try writing it down. Don’t think about what you write; it doesn’t have to be the next great novel; write down your feelings.<br />
 Without realizing it’ll lift your mood.</li>
  <li><strong>Helps you improve your communication skill</strong><br />
 When you write, you turn your abstract ideas into something tangible. It helps you understand yourself and communicate with others.<br />
 You’ll also have clarity and insight about yourself, making it easier to express yourself at any time.</li>
  <li><strong>Helps you sleep better.</strong><br />
 If you let out all your worries and thoughts before you sleep, you’ll get much better sleep than ever.<br />
 Researchers believe that letting out all the disturbing thoughts before you go to sleep helps you sleep better at night.</li>
  <li><strong>Helps you learn from your mistakes</strong><br />
 As humans, we’re constantly making choices, and those choices sometimes end up being mistakes. Making mistakes is good because it helps us grow, but repeating the same error frustrates us. <br />
 Writing in a journal will help you identify and be aware of those mistakes next time.</li>
  <li><strong>Understand yourself better.</strong><br />
 One of the most beneficial things journalling can do is help you better understand yourself. <br />
 It enables you to keep track of everything in your life, making you better understand yourself.</li>
</ol>

<p>These are just the tip of the iceberg. Once you incorporate journalling into your life, you’ll see many benefits.  <br />
If you’re starting journaling or want some tips on how to keep one, keep reading. I have some for you.</p>

<h3 id="simple-steps-to-start-journaling">Simple steps to start journaling</h3>
<ol>
  <li><strong>Choose a medium to write</strong><br />
 Everyone has a preference here. Choose what suits you best: a traditional notebook or a digital app. <br />
 Just choose one and experiment with it.</li>
  <li><strong>Find a comfortable space</strong><br />
 It’s time to talk to yourself, so you don’t need anyone to bother you. It is your me time. <br />
 Choosing a quiet and comfortable place will help you to think deeply and write clearly.</li>
  <li><strong>Create a routine</strong><br />
Establishing a routine can greatly enhance your mental health while journaling. <br />
It’s beneficial to have a consistent routine, whether it’s in the early morning or at night.</li>
  <li><strong>Be authentic</strong> <br />
 It is your private space; no one will see and judge you, so be true to your writing. <br />
 Don’t worry about your grammar, the length of your entries, spelling, or writing style. <br />
 What matters is that you’ve stayed true to yourself.
<img src="/assets/images/sticky-idea.png" alt="sticky-idea" />
    <h3 id="tips-on-journaling">Tips on journaling</h3>
    <p>Here are some tips to help you in your journaling.</p>
  </li>
  <li><strong>Review your day</strong><br />
 You can review your day while you journal. Ask yourself questions about how your day went out, what went as planned, what didn’t go well, what did you achieve, etc.<br />
 I do this every day, and it helps me understand what’s working and what’s not.</li>
  <li><strong>Mood journaling</strong><br />
 Not everyone is good at talking about their feelings, so keeping a mood journal helps us express our thoughts and emotions without anyone judging us.</li>
  <li><strong>Wish lists and bucket lists.</strong><br />
 What do you wish to have? What have you always wanted to do? <br />
 Keeping a list of those things will help you understand whether you’re living the life you want to live.</li>
  <li><strong>Write your goals.</strong><br />
 Substantial research suggests that writing down goals has a significantly more significant effect than not writing them down.<br />
 These studies collectively suggest that writing down goals enhances clarity, motivation, and accountability, making them more likely to be achieved.<br />
 Write down your goals to have a better chance of achieving them.</li>
  <li><strong>Write a letter from your future self</strong><br />
 It will help you understand what you want to become in the future.</li>
  <li><strong>Explore different journalling style</strong><br />
 Experiment with different types of journaling to find what best suits your needs. <br />
 Different styles can offer new perspectives and benefits, Whether bullet journaling, stream of consciousness, or structured reflective writing.</li>
</ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Productivity" /><category term="Journalling" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have always been a massive fan of writing for personal use. For that reason, I have been journaling since I was 16. Initially, I didn’t know what to write about, but eventually, when I kept writing, it changed my life. So, I am presenting you with a 30-day challenge to try journalling and see how it changes your life. If you’re wondering how keeping a journal might benefit you, here are some that may help you: Benefits of Journalling. Makes you boost your mood. If you’re feeling down or having a rough day, try writing it down. Don’t think about what you write; it doesn’t have to be the next great novel; write down your feelings. Without realizing it’ll lift your mood. Helps you improve your communication skill When you write, you turn your abstract ideas into something tangible. It helps you understand yourself and communicate with others. You’ll also have clarity and insight about yourself, making it easier to express yourself at any time. Helps you sleep better. If you let out all your worries and thoughts before you sleep, you’ll get much better sleep than ever. Researchers believe that letting out all the disturbing thoughts before you go to sleep helps you sleep better at night. Helps you learn from your mistakes As humans, we’re constantly making choices, and those choices sometimes end up being mistakes. Making mistakes is good because it helps us grow, but repeating the same error frustrates us. Writing in a journal will help you identify and be aware of those mistakes next time. Understand yourself better. One of the most beneficial things journalling can do is help you better understand yourself. It enables you to keep track of everything in your life, making you better understand yourself.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/writing-journal.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/writing-journal.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Digital Declutter Why and How to Simplify Your Digital Life</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Digital-Declutter-Why-and-How-to-Simplify-Your-Digital-Life/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Digital Declutter Why and How to Simplify Your Digital Life" /><published>2024-12-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Digital%20Declutter%20Why%20and%20How%20to%20Simplify%20Your%20Digital%20Life</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Digital-Declutter-Why-and-How-to-Simplify-Your-Digital-Life/"><![CDATA[<p>You must have decluttered your house or room at least once in your lifetime, but what about your digital life? 
Have you ever been overwhelmed by the number of emails you have left unread, the number of apps on your phone that you don’t even use, or the files on your laptop that have been there for years without you even knowing what they are? 
Decluttering your digital life will not only help you have a clean space but also help you reclaim focus and be productive.</p>

<p>Digital decluttering simplifies and organizes our digital life aspect to reduce stress and improve efficiency.
If you see these signs in your daily life, consider decluttering your digital life for a better life.</p>
<ul>
  <li>You get overwhelmed by notifications</li>
  <li>Your inbox has 1000+ unread emails.</li>
  <li>Finding files on your computer takes forever.</li>
</ul>

<p><em>Let’s discuss how you can start decluttering your digital life in straightforward steps.</em></p>

<h3 id="step-1-audit-your-digital-space">Step 1: Audit your digital space</h3>
<p>First, review every aspect of your digital life, including emails, apps, folders, and social media, and identify disorganization.                                                            <br />
It’s important to know what we’re decluttering before we start our work, so take your time and identify which ones you need to declutter since everyone is different.</p>

<h3 id="step-2-declutter-your-inbox">Step 2: Declutter your inbox</h3>
<p>How many emails have you subscribed to and forgotten they even exist? We almost always use our emails, and our inboxes are filled with both important and unimportant stuff.                                                       <br />
You need to review the emails you don’t need any longer and unsubscribe them. 
You can also organize your emails by using filters, delete old and unnecessary emails, or archive them if you’re not sure whether you need them in the future.</p>

<h3 id="step-3-organize-digital-files">Step 3: Organize digital files</h3>
<p>There are many ways to organize your digital files, but Tiago Forte’s PARA method is more practical. 
PARA is a method of organizing your files, and I will explain what each letter represents in a second.</p>

<p><strong>P is for Projects;</strong> this is where you store everything you’re currently working on.<br />
<strong>A is for Areas;</strong> anything related to your life goes here, including personal documents like copies of your IDs, taxes, etc.<br />
<strong>R stands for Resources;</strong> you will store any resources you use for your projects here. After you finish your projects, you can move them to this folder.<br />
<strong>A is for Archives;</strong> here are things you might need in the future but don’t need now.</p>

<p>You don’t strictly have to follow these rules; they’re a good starting point for your organization. The point is to have an organized file system that will help you be productive.<br />
<em>Always remember to back up your files ALWAYS.</em>
<img src="/assets/images/iphone-apps.png" alt="Iphone apps" /></p>

<h3 id="step-4-apps">Step 4: Apps</h3>
<p>I am sure there are tons of apps on your phone you don’t use. We always use our phones, and if they’re messy, we can get distracted easily.<br />
Besides, having a clean and organized phone feels good.</p>

<ul>
  <li>Delete unused apps on your phone; it will save up space for you while leaving you to declutter.</li>
  <li>Go through your files and back up the necessary ones.</li>
  <li>Turn off unnecessary notifications.</li>
  <li>Lastly, only put essential apps on your home screen to have quick access to them.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="step-5-social-media">Step 5 Social media</h3>
<p>You may be wondering why I put social media here.
We use social media to get valuable and entertaining content. While following an account with an idea we don’t support might be suitable for being critical, we don’t have to follow accounts full of negative content. <br />
If we feel bad after being on social media for minutes, we might unfollow those accounts.</p>

<p>Go to your every social media account and unfollow those who don’t bring you value.<br />
While you unfollow those who don’t bring you value, consider following <strong>ThinkFlow</strong> on <a href="https://instagram.com/thinkflowme">Instagram</a> and <a href="twitter.com/thinkflowme">Twitter/X</a> for helpful content. <br />
<em>(You can unfollow us if we don’t get you any value)</em></p>

<p>Don’t just declutter your digital life once and forget about it. Set a regular schedule to review it. It doesn’t have to be every day or every week but don’t forget to review it regularly before it gets messy again.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Produtivity" /><category term="Minimalism" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[You must have decluttered your house or room at least once in your lifetime, but what about your digital life? Have you ever been overwhelmed by the number of emails you have left unread, the number of apps on your phone that you don’t even use, or the files on your laptop that have been there for years without you even knowing what they are? Decluttering your digital life will not only help you have a clean space but also help you reclaim focus and be productive.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/smart-watch.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/smart-watch.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Best Ergonomic Workspace Setups on a Budget</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Best-Ergonomic-Workspace-Setups-on-a-Budget/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Best Ergonomic Workspace Setups on a Budget" /><published>2024-12-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Best%20Ergonomic%20Workspace%20Setups%20on%20a%20Budget</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Best-Ergonomic-Workspace-Setups-on-a-Budget/"><![CDATA[<p>You can establish an optimal desk workspace that significantly enhances your productivity without straining your budget. With careful planning and strategic purchases, you can create a comfortable and functional home office or study area for <strong><em>under $400.</em></strong></p>

<p>This setup can include essential components such as a well-designed desk, an ergonomic chair to support long work hours, adequate lighting to reduce eye strain, and organizational tools to tidy your workspace.</p>

<p>Investing in these key items will improve your efficiency and ensure you feel secure in your financial decisions, allowing you to focus entirely on your tasks. Will list quality workspace setups on budget.</p>
<h4 id="desk">Desk</h4>
<p>An appropriate desk is essential for maintaining an efficient and productive work environment. A well-designed, minimalist, functional desk can significantly enhance your focus and the aesthetics of your workspace.</p>

<p><a href="https://amzn.to/3Dly9Xg">VASAGALE Computer Desk</a> offers a spacious and sturdy tabletop suitable for a computer and other office essentials and includes eight hooks specifically designed for cable management. <br />
This thoughtful feature helps prevent cable clutter, ensuring your desk is organized and visually appealing. <br />
Investing in a desk like this creates a more conducive atmosphere for concentration and creativity.</p>

<h4 id="chair">Chair</h4>
<p>Investing in a chair that balances affordability with comfort and promotes good posture becomes crucial when you work long hours at a desk. <br />
<a href="https://amzn.to/4gvMSxd">The BestOffice Ergonomic Chair</a> is meticulously designed with your well-being in mind, ensuring that you remain comfortable, even during those marathon work sessions.</p>

<p>This chair features thoughtfully crafted cushions and armrests, meticulously engineered to align with the contours of the human body. <br />
This ergonomic design allows you to settle into the chair and find the perfect fit, promoting healthy posture and reducing the chance of discomfort or strain over long periods of sitting.</p>

<p>Moreover, the chair’s construction is intended for prolonged use, making it a durable choice for anyone who spends significant hours at their desk.<br />
It boasts a new metal base that enhances its stability and longevity and contributes a touch of modern aesthetic appeal to your workspace.</p>

<p>With the <a href="https://amzn.to/4gvMSxd">BestOffice Ergonomic Chair</a>, you can work efficiently and comfortably, ensuring that your work environment supports your productivity and health.
<img src="/assets/images/girl-with-laptop.png" alt="girl with laptop" /></p>
<h4 id="desk-lamp">Desk Lamp</h4>
<p>Light is vital in enhancing productivity and maintaining focus while you work or study. After researching various options, I discovered that one of the most affordable yet high-quality lighting solutions is <a href="https://amzn.to/4izN4x8">Lepro’s Desk Lamp</a>.</p>

<p>A standout feature of this lamp is its C-Clamp design, which allows it to be securely attached to the edge of your desk, freeing up valuable workspace and minimizing clutter.</p>

<p>Additionally, the lamp offers three distinct color modes—warm light, incredible light, and natural daylight—to suit different tasks or personal preferences. <br />
You can easily switch modes if you need a cozy ambiance for reading or a bright light for detailed work.</p>

<p>Moreover, it provides about ten brightness levels, enabling you to customize the intensity of the light to match your needs throughout the day. <br />
With this desk lamp, you’ll find that you can create the perfect lighting environment to boost your productivity and enhance your focus.</p>
<h4 id="monitor">Monitor</h4>
<p>In the modern work environment, leveraging a second monitor can significantly elevate your productivity levels. <br />
With the added screen space, you can organize your workflow more effectively, allowing for an expansive view of multiple documents, applications, and web pages simultaneously.</p>

<p>This seamless setup minimizes the hassle of constantly switching between tabs and provides a more fluid and efficient working experience.<br />
Moreover, creating an ergonomic workstation is essential for your overall health and comfort. <br />
An ergonomic setup includes adjustable chairs, desks at the right height, and monitors positioned to reduce physical strain. <br />
By prioritizing good posture, you can effectively minimize neck and back discomfort, making long work hours much more bearable.</p>

<p>If you’re seeking a budget-friendly display that doesn’t compromise on quality, <a href="https://amzn.to/3ZvDvqC">Acer’s 21-inch computer monitor</a> is an exceptional choice. <br />
This monitor features vibrant colors and sharp clarity, making it perfect for everything from spreadsheet analysis to graphic design. <br />
Its sleek, modern design complements any workspace while providing reliable performance, ensuring you get the best return on your investment and ultimately enjoy a more productive workday.</p>

<p>Using a second monitor enhances productivity by providing additional screen space. An ergonomic desk setup helps maintain good posture and reduces neck strain. <a href="https://amzn.to/3ZvDvqC">Acer’s 21-inch computer monitor</a> offers the best value for those on a budget.</p>
<h4 id="mouse">Mouse</h4>
<p>Investing in a budget-friendly yet high-performing mouse is crucial for enhancing your computing experience. <br />
Look for a model with a comfortable grip and programmable buttons, making it ideal for work tasks and casual gaming sessions. <br />
One standout option is the <a href="https://amzn.to/3DbBJ6t">Logitech G350</a>, recognized as one of the most affordable mice available without compromising quality.</p>

<h4 id="additional-accessories">Additional Accessories</h4>
<p>Incorporating various accessories into your setup can significantly enhance both functionality and aesthetics. <br />
For instance, the <a href="https://amzn.to/3VC5402">KTRIO’s mouse pad</a> is designed to be water-resistant and non-slip, providing a stable surface for your mouse while adding a touch of style to your workspace.</p>

<p>To further personalize your environment, consider adding vibrant plants, cherished photo frames, or unique decorations that reflect your personality and inspire creativity.</p>

<p>For just under $400, you can create an ideal workspace that enhances your productivity and fosters creativity. <br />
This budget allows you to invest in a comfortable ergonomic chair, a spacious desk accommodating your equipment, and essential organizational tools to keep your area clutter-free.</p>

<p>Additionally, consider adding lighting and personal touches that make the space inviting and inspiring. This thoughtful setup can significantly improve your focus and efficiency while working.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Productivity" /><category term="Product" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can establish an optimal desk workspace that significantly enhances your productivity without straining your budget. With careful planning and strategic purchases, you can create a comfortable and functional home office or study area for under $400.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/workspace.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/workspace.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Reading Resolutions: Top Books to Change Your Life in 2025</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Reading-Resolutions-Top-Books-to-Change-Your-Life-in-2025/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Reading Resolutions: Top Books to Change Your Life in 2025" /><published>2024-12-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Reading%20Resolutions:%20Top%20Books%20to%20Change%20Your%20Life%20in%202025</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Reading-Resolutions-Top-Books-to-Change-Your-Life-in-2025/"><![CDATA[<h3 id="introduction">Introduction</h3>

<p>2025 is here, and most of us plan to read more books when the new year comes. There are thousands of books to read, but if you’re wondering which books are worth reading to change your life, come along with me because I will list the top 5 books you should read in 2025 that will change your life.</p>

<p><strong>Quick disclaimer:</strong> These books may sound cliché because you have seen them everywhere, but trust me, if you haven’t read them yet, give them a try.</p>

<h4 id="1-why-we-sleep-unlocking-the-power-of-sleep-and-dreams-by-matthew-walker">1. Why We Sleep: Unlocking the Power of Sleep and Dreams by Matthew Walker</h4>

<p>Matthew Walker is no ordinary man. He is a sleep scientist who has studied how sleep affects our physical and mental well-being.</p>

<p>This book will help you understand why we sleep, how sleep affects our daily lives, and, more importantly, how to optimize sleep.</p>

<p>Get the book on <a href="https://amzn.to/3BkuW9Z">amazon</a></p>

<h4 id="2-the-subtle-art-of-not-giving-a-fck-a-counterintuitive-approach-to-living-a-good-life-by-mark-manson">2. The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck: A Counterintuitive Approach to Living a Good Life by Mark Manson</h4>

<p>This one is different because it challenges the modern self-help industry’s focus on the positive, arguing that the key to a fulfilling life is not about having everything you want but about focusing on what matters.</p>

<p>It offers a great perspective on prioritizing what matters most and accepting our limitations.</p>

<p>This book suits those who want a more honest and no-nonsense approach to life.</p>

<p>Mark also has a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@IAmMarkManson">YouTube</a> channel with over 2.5 Million subscribers where he talks about a lot of no-nonsense self-help advice.</p>

<p>Get the book on <a href="https://amzn.to/3D6I0QP">amazon</a></p>

<h4 id="3-building-a-second-brain-a-proven-method-to-organize-your-digital-life-and-unlock-your-creative-potential-by-tiago-forte">3. Building a Second Brain: A Proven Method to Organize Your Digital Life and Unlock Your Creative Potential by Tiago Forte</h4>

<p>This book introduces a new concept called “second brain,” a method for capturing, organizing, and leveraging your information to increase productivity and mental clarity.</p>

<p>It discusses digital tools and techniques to create a personalized productivity system.</p>

<p>If you’re overwhelmed by the sheer volume of information in your digital life, this book provides practical strategies for better organizations. It’s especially useful for knowledge workers, students, and anyone looking to get more out of their digital tools.</p>

<p>Tiago also has a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@TiagoForte">YouTube</a> video in which he talks about similar things about productivity and interviews people who read his book and created their own “Second brain.” I highly recommend checking it out.</p>

<p>Get the book on <a href="https://amzn.to/49tLn0s">amazon</a></p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/books-color.png" alt="colorful books" /></p>

<h4 id="4-mans-search-for-meaning-by-viktor-e-frankl">4. Man’s Search for Meaning by Viktor E. Frankl</h4>

<p>In this book, Viktor shares his experience as a Holocaust survivor and his philosophy of finding meaning in all forms of suffering. He explores the concept of existentialism and how to live a life filled with purpose through his narrative and psychological insight.</p>

<p>This book is a deep psychological read that can help readers better understand their own lives and the meaning of suffering.</p>

<p>Get the book on <a href="https://amzn.to/3OLmC64">amazon</a></p>

<h4 id="5-feel-good-productivity-how-to-do-more-of-what-matters-to-you-by-ali-abdaal">5. Feel-Good Productivity: How to Do More of What Matters to You by Ali Abdaal</h4>

<p>Last but not least, Ali Abdaal’s book explores the concept of productivity as a means to get more done and a tool to live a more meaningful and fulfilling life.</p>

<p>He discusses the importance of aligning productivity with personal values, helping readers focus on what truly matters in life.</p>

<p>It provides practical advice on managing time and energy, improving habits, and achieving balance and well-being. It is perfect for those struggling with conventional productivity systems and looking to create a more fulfilling life.</p>

<p>Ali also has a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@aliabdaal">YouTube</a> channel where he discusses various productivity topics.</p>

<p>Get the book on <a href="https://amzn.to/3Zhlzji">amazon</a></p>

<h3 id="summary">Summary</h3>

<p>This short list of books is to help you start somewhere; you don’t have to think too much about which book you should read; pick one that interests you and start reading. If you find value after reading 10% of the books, keep reading. If not, leave that book and start something or read a summary about it on blogs or platforms like <a href="https://www.shortform.com/">Shortform</a>, which provides a comprehensive summary of non-fiction books.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p><strong>Disclaimer</strong>: I earn a small commission when you buy a product using the links I provided at no cost. Thank You.</p>
</blockquote>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Productivity" /><category term="books" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/books-front.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/books-front.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>